♬ 引き合うように 重なる波紋
I found what I was searching for, Dio!
And now I have proof of your devilish conspiracy!
♬～
He's got me backed into a corner...
♬ 誇りの道を往く者に
太陽の導きを
But I will not submit!
I returned to make sure that Jojo was dealt with once and for all!
♬ 野望の果てを目指す者に
生け贄を
♬～
♬ 震えるほど心
燃え尽きるほど熱く
Sora koboreochita futatsu no hoshi ga
Two stars fall from the sky
♬ その手から放て 鼓動
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Hikari to yami no minamo suikomareteyuku
One shining in the light, the other sinking into darkness
♬ 身体 漲る勇気で
♬ 迷いなき覚悟に喝采を
Hikiau you ni kasanaru hamon
A ripple drawing the two of them together
♬ その血の運命 ジョジョ
Quality Check:
Tonitonichopchop
Hokori no michi wo yuku mono ni taiyou no michibiki wo
One will walk the path of pride and receive the sun's guidance
♬～
Yabou no hate wo mezasu mono ni
One will walk the path of unbridled ambition...
Ikenie wo
Demanding sacrifice!
Furueru hodo kokoro moetsukiru hodo atsuku
Let that burning in your soul calm the trembling of your heart
Timing/Typesetting/Encoding:
Fadeout4
Sono te kara hanate kodou
Strike down your fears,
Karada minagiru yuuki de
With courage coursing through your veins!
Mayou naki kakugo ni kassai wo
You cannot overcome your pain unless you can accept...
Sono chi no sadame
The legacy of your bloodline!
Jojo!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
Episode 3: "My Youth With Dio"
I was able to find the antidote...
解毒剤は 手に入れたよ｡
さっき 父さんに飲ませた｡
I've already given it to my father.
ディオ… 僕は 気が重い｡
Dio... this pains me.
兄弟同様に育った 君を➡
I never expected to have to deliver the man who was raised to be my brother over to the police.
これから 警察へ突き出さなくては
いけないなんて 残念だよ｡
It's a shame... Dio...
ディオ 分かってもらえないかも
しれないが これは 本心だよ｡
You probably don't believe me, but that is how I honestly feel.
はぁ…｡
その気持ち 君らしい優しさだ｡
This is the kindness I've come to expect from you.
ジョジョ 勝手だけど 頼みがある｡
最後の頼みなんだ｡
Jojo... I realize it's selfish, but I have one last request...
Please, let me have some time...
僕に 時間をくれないか？
警察に 自首する時間を！
Just enough so I can surrender myself to the police!
《えっ？ 意外！➡
Unbelievable!
I was certain that he would struggle, attacking like a cornered beast!
てっきり
追い詰められた 野獣のごとく➡
反撃に出ると 警戒していたが》
Jojo...
《ジョジョ～！➡
How in the bloody hell did you escape from the slums alive?
無事に
あの貧民街から 戻るとは！➡
I have no other choice...
もう 殺るしかない！➡
I'll have to wait until he lowers his guard,
then gut him with my knife!
油断させて 一気に
ナイフで ぶっ殺してやる！》
Please, I regret the wicked life I've led up until now!
僕は悔いているんだ｡
今までの人生を！
貧しい環境に 生まれ育ったんで➡
I was born into poverty, and it led me to pursue such foolish ambitions!
くだらん野心を
持ってしまったんだ！
I've been such an idiot!
バカなことを しでかしたよ！
The fact that I would harm my benefactor over his fortune...  after all the kindness he's shown me...
育ててもらった恩人に
毒を盛って 財産を奪おうなんて｡
I returned here because I wanted to turn myself in!
その証しに 自首するために
戻ってきたんだよ！
逃亡しようと思えば 外国でも
どこへでも 行けたはずなのに！
Why else would I return when I could have fled anywhere in the world?!
た… 確かに｡
Th-that's true...
I want to pay for my crimes...
罪の償いがしたいんだ！
ディオ…｡
Dio...
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
ジョースターさん 気を付けろ｡➡
I'd be careful, Mr. Joestar.
You can't trust a word this scoundrel says!
信じるなよ そいつの言葉を！
ヌムッ!?
誰だ？ って表情してんで➡
You must be wondering who I am...
自己紹介させてもらうがよ｡
Allow me to introduce myself...
俺は おせっかい焼きの
スピードワゴン！
Speedwagon's the name, and meddling's my game!
ロンドンの貧民街から
ジョースターさんが 心配なんで➡
I met the good Mr. Joestar here in the slums of London, so I accompanied him to help keep an eye out.
くっついて来た｡
Mr. Joestar, I've grown fond of you and your naiveté, so let me tell you something...
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
ジョースターさん アマちゃんの
あんたが 好きだから➡
１つ 教えてやるぜ！
I've lived in the underworld my entire life,
and I've met scoundrels of every sort.
俺は 生まれてから
ずっと 暗黒街で生き➡
いろんな悪党を 見てきた｡
だから 悪い人間と いい人間の
区別は においで分かる！➡
I can tell a good man from a rotten one just by their scent...
こいつは 臭え！➡
This bastard stinks!
He reeks worse than the lowest gutter trash I've ever met!
ゲロ以下の においが
プンプンするぜ！
こんなワルには
出会ったことがねえほどな！
I've never met a scoundrel of his caliber in my entire life!
So you say your upbringing turned you into a bastard?
環境で悪人になっただと？
違うね！➡
A likely story!
You've been evil since the day you were born!
こいつは 生まれついてのワルだ！
Perhaps, you recall... this face?!
この顔に 見覚えがあるだろ！
This easterner confessed to selling you the poison.
この東洋人が 君に毒薬を売った
証言は 取ってある｡
ぐっ…｡
≪(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)話は聞いたよ｡
I heard everything...
あっ！
I am truly sorry...
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)残念でならない｡
君には 息子と同じくらいの愛情と
期待を込めたつもりだったが…｡
I tried to raise you with the same
hope and affection as I have for my own son...
ぐっ…｡
父さん まだ 安静にしていないと｡
Father, you shouldn't be out of bed!
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)
ああ… 寝室へ行って休むよ｡
Very well... I shall return to my room.
I have no desire to see my son taken away in chains.
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)息子が捕まるのを
見たくはない｡➡
Jojo, please see to the rest.
ジョジョ 後は頼む｡
はい｡
Yes, father.
I suppose this is the end, then...
さすがに もう おしまいか｡
That boy will not be detained.
(ﾜﾝﾁｪﾝ)あの男 捕まりやせんよ｡
I can see it written on his face, evident by the three birthmarks on his ear...
耳の３つのほくろに 顔の相｡
やつは 強運の下に
生まれついとる｡
He was born under the star of great fortune.
ジョジョ せめて
君の手で 手錠を掛けてほしい｡
Jojo... the least you could do is
be the one to put the cuffs on me.
For everything we've been through these seven years...
７年間の つきあいで…｡
分かった｡
Okay...
Watch yourself, Mr. Joestar!
ジョースターさん
気を付けなせえ｡
ジョジョ… 人間ってのは
能力に限界があるな｡
Jojo... I suppose there are limits to the abilities of humankind...
俺が 短い人生で 学んだことは
人間は 策を弄すれば弄するほど➡
If there is one thing I have learned in my short life...
The more you plot and scheme, the less likely it becomes things will go according to plan...
予期せぬ事態で
策が崩れ去るってことだ｡
人間を超えるものにならねばな｡
One would have to be more than human to overcome that...
何のことだ？ 何を言っている!?
What are you saying? What do you mean?!
俺は 人間をやめるぞ！
ジョジョ！
I'm through with being a mere mortal, Jojo!
俺は 人間を超越する！
I will transcend humanity!
The stone mask?! Why do you have it?!
石仮面!? なぜ 君が!?
Watch out!
危ない！
(警部)やつを射殺しろ！
Shoot him!
ジョジョ お前の血でだ！
And I'll use your blood to do it, Jojo!
ああ… あっ！
ああ…｡
That's...
これは!?
Father!
父さ～ん‼
フフフ…｡
フハハハ…｡
フハハハッ！ ハハハハッ！
Fire!
撃て～！
(銃声)
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)ジョジョ…｡
Jojo...
F-Father...
と… 父さん｡
ああ… ナイフなんて
普通なら よけられたのに｡
I could have dodged that knife...
But I was so distracted by the stone mask...
僕が
石仮面に 気を取られたから｡
僕の身代わりに…｡
And in my stead, you...
Take this...
これを…｡
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)死んだ母さんの指輪だ｡
This ring belonged to your late mother...
Father!
父さん！
うう…
あのナイフの位置は 急所｡
That knife wound is most certainly fatal...
Damn it, I was supposed to keep this from happening!
くそっ！ 俺が付いていながら｡
(警部)ああ… ジョースター卿！
Lord Joestar! This is what I was talking about!
だから あのとき 言ったのに｡➡
わしの責任だ｡
わしが あのとき➡
This is my fault! If only I had thrown Dio Brando's father behind bars!
ディオ･ブランドーの父親を
流島の刑にしていれば！
His father...?
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
ディオ･ブランドーの父親？
わしが 警察の仕事に就いて
間もないころ｡➡
It wasn't long after I joined the police force that we caught a man who was trying to sell a stolen ring...
あの指輪を 質に流そうとし
逮捕された男がいた｡➡
それが ディオの父親
ダリオ･ブランドーだ！
That man was Dio's father... Dario Brando!
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)《確かに 私の指輪だ》
Indeed, this matches my ring...
My wife and I had a matching pair made especially for us.
《婚約のときに
妻と そろいで 作った…》
(警部)
《ブランドーという こそ泥が➡
We caught a thief by the name of Brando trying to sell it.
質に流そうとしている
寸前でした》
Brando?!
《ブランドー…》
(警部)
ブランドーは ジョースター卿の
命の恩人ということだった｡➡
Lord Joestar thought Brando had saved his life...
But it was all a ruse!
だが とんでもない！
やつは 馬車の事故を幸い➡
He was just a sneaky rat who tried to loot the wreckage of an accident!
金品を あさっていた
こずるい悪党だったのだ！
Bloody hell!
(ﾀﾞﾘｵ)《ヤベえ！》
Tell me... Did he say that I had willingly given him that ring?
《君 彼は
こう 言わなかったかね？➡
｢この指輪は
私から もらった｣と》
(警部)《ええ 言いましたとも！
とんでもない うそをね！》
Yes sir, that he did!
What a load of rubbish!
《いや うそではない｡
この指輪は 彼に贈った物だ》
That was no lie...
I sent him that ring.
W-What are you saying?!
《な… 何ですって!?》
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)《彼は無実だ｡
釈放してやってくれたまえ》
He's innocent.
There is no reason to detain him.
《なぜ!?
なぜ そんな でたらめを!?》
Why?! Why would you let him get away with this?!
《私も 貧困の中に生まれたら➡
I might have done the same thing, had I been born into poverty...
同じことを
していたかもしれない》
Please take this... Sell it, and buy something for your family.
《これを売って 家族に
何か 買ってやってください｡➡
And please... Turn your life around, do not stray from the path of good.
そして もう 悪の人ではなく
善の人になるのです》
(警部)ジョースター卿は
全てを知った上で➡
Lord Joestar knew the truth, and he still agreed to take Dio in!
ディオを 養子にしたのだ｡
Father, please stay strong... The doctors can save you!
父さん… しっかり｡
医者が来れば 助かります｡
ジョジョ
ディオを 恨まないでやってくれ｡
Jojo, please don't hold this against Dio...
私が悪かったのだ｡
This was all my fault...
(ｼﾞｮｰｽﾀｰ卿)実の息子ゆえに
お前には 厳しくしたが➡
I was far too strict, even with you...
ディオの気持ちからすると➡
I can only imagine how that must have made Dio feel...
かえって
不平等に感じたかもしれない｡
それが 彼を このようなことに
仕向けたのだろう｡➡
It must have pushed him to do this...
Please... bury Dio alongside his father.
ディオは ブランドー氏のそばに
葬ってやってくれ｡
父さん｡
Father...
悪くないぞ ジョジョ…｡
It's not so bad, Jojo... Being able to die...
息子の腕の中で
死んでいくと… いう… のは…｡
In the arms of... my son...
(一同)ジョースター卿！
Lord Joestar!
う… う…｡
あの優しさが こんな…｡
It was his kindness that led to all of this! It was all for nothing!
間違いだったんだ｡
死んでしまったら おしまいじゃ！
You're wrong!
違う！➡
あの父親の精神は➡
That man's kind-hearted spirit has been
passed down to his son, Jonathan Joestar!
息子のジョナサン･ジョースターが
立派に 受け継いでいる！➡
It will become the flame that drives him, his source of strength, lighting the path to his future!
それは 彼の強い意志となり
誇りとなり 未来となるだろうぜ！
Normally, I can't stand naïve fools who cry whenever life sends hardship their way...
普通 俺は 自分が困ると
すぐ 泣き抜かす アマちゃんは➡
大嫌いだがよ｡
この親子は違う｡➡
But this family is an exception...
They have absolute faith in their course of action! They're true men, through and through!
自分たちのしたことを 後悔しない
最高の大アマちゃんだぜ！
The... the body!
し… 死体が…
ディオ･ブランドーの死体がない！
Where is Dio Brando's body?!
Constable, get away from that window!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
警察の旦那！ 窓から離れろ！
グハッ！
グホッ！
Wrrryyyyyy...
UREEYYY！
The constable's head!
(警察官１)警部の頭が…｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)な… 何だ？ こいつは!?
生き返ってる！
W-What's the meaning of this?! How is he still alive?!
(警察官２)なぜだ!?
あんなに 弾丸を食らったのに｡
How could he survive those gunshots?!
Be careful! He must have a weapon on him!
(警察官１)気を付けろ！
何か 武器を持ってるに違いない｡
I-Impossible!
ま… まさか…｡
H-He's heading this way...
(警察官３)
こ… こっちに 向かってくるぞ！
What are you doing? Shoot him!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
何してる!? 早く 狙撃しろ！
Dio, stop!
ディオ 止まれ！
ディ… ディオ～！
D-Dio!
危険だ ジョジョ！
早く撃て！ 撃つんだ‼
Don't be reckless, Jojo! Just shoot him! You have to!
(銃声)
あっ！
うっ！
うう…｡
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)うわ～！
He... He's still alive... He was shot in the head, and he's still...
し… 死なねえ｡
頭を撃たれたのに｡
What is this...
俺には 分からねえ｡
What's going on?! Because I haven't the foggiest idea!
今 何が起こっているのか
さっぱり 分からねえ｡
How is this possible?!
なんてことだ！
Jojo!
ジョジョ｡
俺は こんなに 素晴らしい力を
手に入れたぞ！
Witness the incredible power I now possess... I owe it to the stone mask!
石仮面から！
お前の父親の血から！
Not to mention your father's blood!
ヒュー｡
ギャー！
Wrrrryyy!
UUURRRRYYY！
He's draining his blood... and drawing energy from it?!
吸い取っているのか!?
人間の精気を！
ディオは 一体
何者になってしまったんだ!?
What happened that you turned into this, Dio?!
(警察官２)うわ～！
ゲッ ゲヴァ！
KUAAA！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)うう… おお…｡
《あ… 頭の中が混乱している｡➡
My head is spinning...
The knife... my father's death... his blood...
ナイフ 父の死 血 ディオ➡
Dio... the stone mask... my research...
石仮面 研究ノート 脳
未知の能力 未知の力｡➡
The brain... strange abilities... untold power!
Is Dio no longer human?
ディオは
もう 人間じゃないのか!?》
URRRY！
Wrryyyy!
Father...
《父さん…》
ハァ～｡
D-Don't!
や… やめろ！
あんたに勝ち目はねえ｡
He's unstoppable!
あんな化け物 見たことねえ｡➡
I've never seen a monster like that before!
I've never seen a beast with that kind of otherworldly power!
あんな
力を超えた力を持つ 魔物はよ！
I know...
ああ｡
To be quite honest, I'm terrified.
正直 僕も怖い｡ だが ディオ！
But Dio...
I cannot allow you to remain in this world!
君を この世に
いさせちゃあいけない！
僕の責任だ｡ 片をつける！
I've inherited this responsibility, and I will put an end to it!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
ジョースターさん やめろ！
殺されるだけだ！
Mr. Joestar, don't! He'll kill you!
《脳！ 石仮面の骨針は
脳から 人間の隠された➡
The brain!
Those spines in the stone mask must unlock some kind of hidden potential in the human brain!
未知の能力を
引き出したに違いない｡➡
とすると
ディオを倒す可能性は…》
Which means there might still be a chance to defeat him...
はっ！
(警察官１)ガヴォガヴォー！➡
血！ うお～！
A corpse!
死体が…｡
(警察官１)あったけえ血｡➡
Blood... I want to lap it up!
ベロベロ なめた～い！
フフ…｡
あっ ああ…｡
(警察官１)でェケケケーッ！
(警察官１)
血 吸ったら いいだろうな！
Blood... just let me drink some of it!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)うわああ～！
ぬおおおおお～ッ！
怪物とはいえ… つらい｡
Monster or not... it still pains me.
父さん… もっと 強い気持ちを
与えてください｡
Father... please give me the strength!
フ～｡
I have to be strong...
《強い意志を持つ！➡
Because Dio isn't human anymore!
ディオは
既に 人間ではないのだから！➡
魔物なのだから！》
He's a demon!
Watch out!
危ない！
KUWAAAAA！
I won't let you slaughter another innocent person!
これ以上 ディオに
殺りくを許すわけにはいか～ん！
と… 止めやがった｡➡
H-He stopped it...
手に串刺して 止めやがった！
It went through his hand and he still stopped it!
And the wound on his head is gone... it's already healed!
そういえば あいつの頭の傷が
治癒している！➡
Immortal... He really is immortal, now!
不死身！ 完全なる不死身！
ぐっ… おお…｡
Weak! You're still a weakling!
貧弱 貧弱！
うあっ！
ぐわっ！
ジョ～ジョ～！
Jojo...
A little more...
もう少し｡
もう少し この素晴らしい力を➡
I'd like to have a little more fun with this magnificent power...
楽しませてもらうぞ｡
I still haven't tested the extent of my abilities, after all...
自分でも どこまで できるか
まだ 分からないからなあ｡
ん？
ふん… 隠れたか｡
Hiding, eh?
ふん｡
フ～｡
言ったろう ジョジョ｡
Remember what I said, Jojo?
策を弄すれば弄するほど
人間には 限界があるのだよ｡
Plot and scheme all you want, humans will always be slaves to their limitations.
無駄な 悪あがきはよせよなあ｡
I would stop struggling if I were you...
カーテンの陰で 怖がってないで
出てこいよ！
Come out from behind that curtain!
UUooooooo！
This isn't some scheme... This is courage!
策ではない！ 勇気だ！
オウウー‼
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ああっ！
焼けながら 組織が再生している｡
His wounds are healing, even though he's on fire!
不死身の理由は これか！
That's the reason behind his immortality!
この火では 倒せない｡
This fire won't be enough to stop him!
うっ うわっ！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)な… 何を!?
What are you doing?!
逃げろ スピードワゴン！
君は もともと 無関係の人間だ！
Get to safety, Speedwagon! This isn't your fight!
ぬうっ！
だあっ！
うう… ぐっ…｡
There's no chance to escape if you go up there!
上へ 逃げちゃあ駄目だ！
火が 屋敷中に広がるぞ！
The fire is spreading to the entire mansion!
うわ～！
Mr. Joestar... what are you thinking?!
《ジョースターさん
何を考えてんだ？》
Come up here, Dio!
上がってくるんだ ディオ｡
はあっ！
ふん｡
Dio! I won't let you and that unearthly power escape into the world!
ディオ！ 君を 君のその力を➡
世の中に 放つわけにはいかない！
ジョースターさん 駄目だ！
Mr. Joestar, don't do it!
ウワッ！ ウワー‼
仲間から 注意をそらすため
俺を誘っているのか｡
You're trying to keep me distracted...
So that your friend can escape...
よかろう｡
Very well.
この やけど お前の命を
吸い取って 治すことにするぞ｡
I'll heal these burns by draining the life from you...
無駄 無駄 無駄 無駄！
Useless, useless, useless, useless!
I can fall from this height and not even feel a thing!
この程度の高さなら
飛び降りても 何ともないのだよ｡
逆に 火と高さに
追い詰められたのは 貴様だ！
And you've just backed yourself into a dead end!
父さん｡
Father...
父さん 悼みます…｡
Father, I'll miss you...
この炎と共に
天国へ行ってください｡ そして…｡
Rise up to heaven, along with these burning embers...
And...
Please lend these flames the strength to do what must be done!
どうか これから
やり遂げることができるように➡
炎に 力をお与えください｡
Mr. Joestar... what are you...
ジョースターさん 一体…｡
No... you can't be planning to...
まさか!? まさか そんな!?
駄目だ！ 駄目だ そんなこと‼
No... you mustn't do what I think you are!
く… 来る！
He's coming!
URRRRRY！
Wrryyyyyyy!
KUA！
オオオゥァー！
Weak! Weak as always!
ええい！ 貧弱 貧弱！
At that moment, Jojo's entire youth flashed before his eyes!
(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)
〈瞬間！ ジョジョの脳裏には
彼自身の青春が…〉
ぐあっ！
My youth... the youth I spent with Dio!
僕の青春は ディオとの青春｡
これから
その青春に 決着をつけてやる！
That youth... ends here, once and for all!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)ジョースターさんは
こう 考えている｡➡
Mr. Joestar wants the fire to burn hotter!
もっと 強い火力ならと！
Hot enough to burn that monster to cinders before he can heal!
あの魔物の回復力が
追いつかないほどの 火力なら➡
Just to defeat Dio!
ディオを倒せると…｡➡
That's why he's gone to the roof, he's waiting for the fire to grow stronger!
そのために
屋敷に 火が広がるまで待って➡
屋根に上ったんだ｡
やめろ～‼
Don't!!
うお～‼
You worm! How dare you!
き… 貴様！
こんなことを よくも！
《僕の祖先たちが 生活した
ジョースター邸が 焼けている｡➡
Joestar Manor... the home I grew up in is burning.
父も死んだ｡ もう 何もない｡➡
My father is dead... I've lost everything... Everything but my life!
全て失った｡ この命以外は》
この命も 燃やし尽くそう！
But I'm willing to see that burn, too!
Whatever it takes, Dio... As long as I can put an end to that twisted power you wield!
引き替えに ディオ！
君の力を封じよう！
くっ…｡
ううっ！
グッバーイ ジョジョ！
Goodbye, Jojo!
うお～‼
It was only for a moment, but your resolve managed to impress me.
ほんの一瞬だが
お前の覚悟には 驚いたぞ｡
父親の死体と共に 死ねて
うれし涙を流しな！ まぬけ！
Now cry tears of joy, for you will be able to die alongside your father!
You buffoon!
《俺は 人間を超えた！➡
I have surpassed humanity! I am immortal, invincible! I can rule the world!
不死身 不老不死｡
俺は この世を支配できる！➡
This is the power you have given me, Jojo!
ジョジョ 貴様がくれた能力だ！》
うわ～‼
おお～！
《足りない！》
Too high!
はあっ！
むっ!?
ディオ！ 戻ってきたぞ！
Dio!
I'm not finished with you!
W-What?! You-
な… 何!? こいつ…｡
I'm not letting go this time!
今度は 離さん！
ディオ！ 君の命運 今 尽きた！
Dio, I'm going to make you face your fate!
With the knife--
ウォー！ このナイフは！
With the knife that you used to kill my father!
このナイフは 君が
父さんに突き立てた ナイフだ‼
うごっ！
ぐあ～！
Wrrryyyyyy!
URYYY‼
うお～！
《こいつ！➡
The bones in both of his arms should be shattered!
両腕の骨を
メチャメチャに砕いたのに！➡
And his body is in flames, so why won't he loosen his grip?!
体に 火がついたのに
力を ほんの少しも 緩めん！》
Very well! Let us plunge into the inferno together!
よ～し いいだろう｡
共に 猛火の中へ
飛び込んでやろう！
But you will be the only one to die!
だがな！ 死ぬのは お前 １人だ！
My body is nigh invulnerable, I have the power to escape the flames no matter how hot they burn!
いくら 火力が強くても➡
脱出できるぐらいの能力は
あるはずさ！
うう… 父さん！ 最後の力を‼
Father!
Give me the last of your strength!
He cries out... A cry that could no longer be heard!
〈叫び！ 無心の叫び！➡
その叫びが
父の魂に通じたのか｡➡
Perhaps his words were able to reach his father's soul...
それとも
生まれ育った 屋敷の構造を➡
Or perhaps he instinctively used the home he grew up in to his advantage.
無意識のうちに
利用していたのか｡➡
蹴った！
壁を蹴った先には！〉
He kicked!
And after kicking that wall...
《な… 何!?》
W-What?!
The guardian of the Joestar estate:
〈ジョースター家の
守護神！➡
A statue of the Goddess of Love!
慈愛の女神像！〉
ギャー！
うお～！ よくも！
How dare you?! You think you can do this to-
貴様！ こんな… グワー！
わ… 忘れていた｡
I... I forgot...
子供のころから
あった➡
My fatal error... was forgetting the way his anger can explode...
侮っては
いけない やつの爆発力を！
ジョジョ～！
Jojo!
こんなはずでは
俺の人生…｡
It can't end... not like this...
My... life...
ああ！
ジョースターさん！
Mr. Joestar!
Father...
父さん…｡
生きてる｡
生きてるぞ｡➡
You're alive!
He's alive!
この人は… 勝ったんだ～‼
He beat Dio...
He won!
(物音)
I'll be the roundabout
(ﾜﾝﾁｪﾝ)ウウウヘ ウヘヘ！
あったね｡
The words will make you out 'n' out
I'll spend the day your way
ギャアアアアーッ！
Call it morning driving through the sound and
フシュー…｡
In and out the valley
The music dance and sing
They make the children really ring
I'll spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
In and out the valley
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
Twenty-four before my love you'll see I'll be
There with you
(ﾂｪﾍﾟﾘ)勇気とは 怖さを知ること！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)残虐性 異常性において
ディオ以上だ！
(ｼﾞｬｯｸ)絶望に 身をよじれ！
(ｴﾘﾅ)似てるって 誰に？
There it is.
教えてください｡
波紋の使い方を！
Next Episode
Courage comes from knowing true fear!
This guy's more of a freak than Dio!
Let's go, you maggots!
Where have I seen him before?
Please... teach me how to use the Ripple!
Episode 4:
"Overdrive"